

YOVIE ALFAGUISTUTA

Web Developer

ABOUT ME

I am 23 years old and I am a web developer who have 2+ years of experience. Coding on React JS, Laravel and Go Language. I Already serve several clients to build web based applications. My greatest strength in technical terms is problem solving and logical thinking. I am also very enthusiastic and interested to use or learn new things.

SOFT SKILL

- Problem Solving
- Logical Thinking
- Creativty
- Time Management
- Teamwork

TECH STACK

- React JS (Typescript)
- Next JS (Typescript)
- Laravel
- Golang

₩ №

PROGRAMMING TOOLS

- Git
- Redux
- Redux Saga
- Docker & PM2
- Go Fiber
- Postman
- Swagger
- Jest & Cypress
- · Jira & Trello
- Linux
- PostgreeSql
- CI CD
- GIN Gionic

EDUCATION

2017 - 2021 Bachelor degree S1 Informatika (S.Kom)

at Universitas Teknokrat Indonesia,

GPA 3,45.

2015 - 2017 High school graduate from SMAN

5 Bandar Lampung, Science Major

EXPERIENCE

Web Developer Microdata Indonesia 2020 - Present Placed on the Frontend or Backend. Develop multiple applications ranging from government, large enterprises and small businesses with industry standard technology. Most applications are built with React and Laravel. Usually use Golang if the project time is long enough.

Web Developer Freelance 2020 - 2022 Freelancers who are not tied to any companies (External project). The projects such as from UMKM, college assignments and even theses. Applications made such as E-Learning, Payment, Intern Management and others. Everything is made and designed by myself from the beginning to the application until the app ready to launch

Internship Android Developer BAPPEDA (Intern) 2020 Internship for 2 month. Develop 2 Android Mobile Apllication:

- RPJMD
- · UPD

LANGUAGE

Indonesia • • • •

English







Email yoviealfaguistuta@gmail.com



Address

Pulau Sanama Street, Bandar Lampung

